you’re a
ты опять
blogger again no I’m a musician of apples I’m a blogger I
блогер нет я музыкант яблок я блогер я
know I’m sad on purpose so that but I
знаю печалься специально чтобы но мне
didn’t have convenient moments I don’t switch the
было не удобных моментов не я переключаю
table and some sound hissing sound also
столу и некоторых звук шипящий звук тоже
already at home it’s to give why I notice it
аж и доме это дать почему это же замечаю
here I hear you well others hear it
вот я тебя слышу хорошо других слышу
also hisses everything from  what do I depend on and for
тоже шипит все от чего зависит я и за
possible wires and
можно проводов и
next
рядом
to the chairs wires can be a technique of
с кресел провода может быть техника
such quality
такая качество
I hear you perfectly that's what you do
я тебя слышу идеально вот что ты делаешь
in chat roulette and I communicate in different ways I communicate
в чат-рулетке а я разная общаясь общаюсь
with people develop the potential potential of
с людьми развивают потенциал потенциал
which I develop and the canon of
чего развиваюсь и канона
skill communication communication communication
мастерства общение общение
trainings on communication is  you also need to be able
тренинги по общение это тоже нужно уметь
to attend trainings on communication, you spend it on
на тренинги по общение проводишь на
nothing, because I have always been closed
нет я потому что всегда был замкнутый и
and why two of them don’t train, don’t take off your
а почему два из не тренируюсь не сними
glasses so that in the eyes of the interlocutor here is a
очки чтобы в глаза собеседнику здесь
pen, why because I’m a musician, I’m a
ручка почему потому что музыкант я
positron,
позитрон
but I’m just a musician, I’ll come
но я просто музыкант позитрон я приду
to the music and
под музыку и
this is mine  image a without glasses and not written
это мой образ а без очков а не пишется
on no chat roulette no
на нет чат-рулетке нет
there are some some kind of masks I put on yes
есть некоторые какие-то маски одеваю да
clearly they are cool like girls they are
ясно они прикольные нравятся девочки они
people in  life for the first time found such
людей в жизни первый раз нашел такие
cars direct and indirect
тачки прямые и непрямые
communication usually
общение обычно
involves the eye of the eye is
предполагает глаз глаз
not the same hotly the fact is that when we
не та же горячо дело в том что когда мы
speak we speak not only in voice
говорим мы говорим не только голосом
words so terrible look
словами так ужасными взгляде
non-verbal hyperbole when not
невербальный гиперболе когда не
verbal I know this is all I studied too
вербалика я знаю это все я изучал тоже
because I  closed I
потому что я же замкнутый
didn’t
не
write down
записывали
I’m kind I’m kind and I’m writing good
я добрый я добрый чего ли и пишу добрую
music called the phone
музыку называется телефон
it seems
похоже
[music]
[музыка]
it’s not known a song for those who are waiting for a
это не познаешь песня для тех кто ждет
call and we’ll find them
звонка и на их найдем
[music]
[музыка]
everything let’s positron through the fault of one politician
все давай позитрон по вине одна политика
says
говорит
expel tokina
изгонят tokina